Olivia Stokes Hatch papers, 1859-1993 BMC.M86
Bryn Mawr College
- Series I. Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1859-1983
  - Subseries c. Correspondence, 1906-1983
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1933-1934 June (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1934 July-1937 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1938-1940 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1943-1950 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1951-1957 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 19-20)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1964-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1977-1983 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch, undated (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
    - Friends Miscellaneous Letters to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1925-1941 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch and John Davis Hatch Jr. regarding marriage, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 27-29, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch and John Davis Hatch Jr., 1940-1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch and John Davis Hatch Jr., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch and John Davis Hatch Jr., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch and John Davis Hatch Jr., 1967-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Friends to Olivia Stokes Hatch and John Davis Hatch Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Friends to John Davis Hatch Jr., 1939-1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Family Correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
    - Christmas Letters, 1955-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Subseries d. Family Material, 1941-1983
    - Anson Phelps Stokes and Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes social affairs, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Childhood Memorabilia (John Davis Hatch III, Daniel Lindley Hatch, James Stokes Hatch, and Sarah Stokes Hatch), circa 1950s (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
    - Family correspondence regarding Armitage family, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Family Memorabilia, undated (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
    - Fragments, undated (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
    - Itineraries, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Olivia Stokes Hatch Memorabilia, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Printed Matter (magazines, pamphlets, and newsletters), undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Regarding Estate of Carolina Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Regarding Phelps-Stokes Fund (Press releases and reports), 1941-1983 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Third Person Correspondence, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Wills and Estates (Anson Phelps Stokes, Olivia Stokes Hatch, and others), undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified Letters, undated (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
  - Subseries e. Photographs, undated
    - Olivia Stokes Hatch and class, undated (Oversize Rolled Photograph)
    - Cairo, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Egypt, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Foxcroft and Adirondacks, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Southwest, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - album (unidentified), undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Mounted photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 8, Folder 7-13)
- Series II. Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1889-1964
  - Subseries a. Biographical Information, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Subseries b. Correspondence, 1889-1964
    The correspondence in this series is arranged into outgoing and incoming series. This was the pre-existing order and was preserved to maintain order.
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1916 July-1917 May (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1917 June-1917 December (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1918 January-1918 June (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1918 July-1918 November (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1918 December-1919 May (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1916-1920 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1921-1922 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1928-1930 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1931 January-1931 October (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1931 November-1932 August (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1932 September-1936 June (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1936 July-1960 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes-fragments, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Anson Phelps Stokes and Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1916-1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to relatives, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Alma Ruggles, 1916-1933 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to "Cunning" Alma Ruggles, 1918-1939 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Anna V. S. Mitchell to Associates, 1920-1929 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1915-1930 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1933-1960 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Associates, 1922-1926 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Lucy Mitchell Molteno to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1917-1934 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Lucy Mitchell Molteno to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1939-1964 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Carol Williamson to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1924-1964 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Relatives to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1889-1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Alma Ruggles to Anna V. S. Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Friends to Anna V. S. Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - Official Letters to Anna V. S. Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - To Anna V. S. Mitchell (fragments), undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Associates to Anson Phelps Stokes (regarding refugees), 1922-1925 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Associates to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes (regarding refugees), undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Alma Ruggles to her mother and Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1916-1932 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Friends to Alma Ruggles, 1920-1936 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Third person correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Subseries c. Collected Material, undated
    - Publications and notes, undated (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    - Contribution record for Relief Fund, 1930 March-1930 September (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - "Sarre's Islamic Bookbinding"-MS, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Excerpts of Anna V. S. Mitchell Letters-Transcriptions, undated (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - Subseries d. Diaries, 1896-1922
    - 1896-1916 June 15 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1917 February 17-1920 October 27 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 1920 July 23-1922 March 29 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 1922 October 21-1925 February 27 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Subseries e. Essays, undated
    - Assorted, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Fragments, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Fragments and unidentified, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Series III. Family Correspondence, 1868-1927
  Collected Correspondence
  The third and final series, "Family Correspondence," was processed prior to this project. The arrangement assigned during that earlier processing effort was preserved.
  - Alexander to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
  - "Belle" to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - From friends and associates to Clarence Green Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Friends to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 29-34)
  - Friends and associates to Sarah Lindley Mitchell (Box 10, Folder 35, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Friends to Anson Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Friends to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1892-1920 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Friends to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1912-1917 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Friends to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1914-1920 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Friends to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Friends to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, circa 1917 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Friends to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - School Letters and Memorabilia (Stokes Children), circa 1918 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - School Letters and Memorabilia (Stokes Children), 1918-1919 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - School Letters and Memorabilia (Stokes Children), circa 1920 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - School Letters and Memorabilia (Stokes Children), undated (Box 11, Folder 13-15)
  - M.C. Ledyard to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Letters regarding African Missions, 1863-1911 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lindley Family, 1859-1882 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Letters to Lindley Family, 1875-1898 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - J. Bryant Lindley to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1881-1896 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Aunt "Heine" (Mrs. J. Bryant Lindley) to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1880s-1890s (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Lute Lindley to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1881-1892 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Martha (Mattie) Lindley to Sarah Lindley Mitchell and Olivia Eggleston Phelps Stokes, 1868-1908 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Martha Lindley to friends and relatives, 1907-1912 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Mary Lindley to relatives, 1865-1875 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1870-1880 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1875-1899 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Mitchell Family to Sarah Rood, 1896-1900 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Mitchell Family to Sarah Rood, 1896-1900 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Anna V.S. Mitchell to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1889-1915 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Anna V.S. Mitchell to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 11, Folder 32-33)
  - Anna V.S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Anna V.S. Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 11, Folder 35-38)
  - Anna V. S. Mitchell to relatives, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Anna V.S. Mitchell-Fragments, undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Clarence Green Mitchell to Clarence Blair Mitchell, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Clarence Green Mitchell to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1880-1881 March (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Clarence Green Mitchell to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1881 April-1882 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Clarence Green Mitchell to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1883-1886 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Clarence Green Mitchell to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1887-1890 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Lucy Mitchell Molteno to Anna V. S. Mitchell, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Lucy Mitchell Molteno to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1892-1900 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Lucy Mitchell Molteno to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lucy Mitchell Molteno to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to friends and associates, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Clarence Blair Mitchell, 1880-1881 March (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Clarence Blair Mitchell, 1881-1882 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Sarah Green Mitchell, 1883-1884 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Sarah Green Mitchell, 1885-1886 July (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Sarah Green Mitchell, 1886 August-1887 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Sarah Green Mitchell, 1888-1889 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Sarah Green Mitchell, 1890-1898 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1898-1915 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
  - Sarah Lindley Mitchell to relatives, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Relatives and friends to Mary Lindley, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Relatives to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
  - Relatives to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Sarah A. Rood to Sarah Lindley Mitchell and Clarence Blair Mitchell, 1880-1882 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Sarah A. Rood to Sarah Lindley Mitchell and Clarence Blair Mitchell, 1884-1900 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Sarah A. Rood to Nan Mitchell, Lucy Mitchell Molteno, and Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Sarah A. Rood to Clarence Green Mitchell, 1880-1881 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sarah A. Rood to Sarah Lindley Mitchell and Clarence Blair Mitchell, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Stokes Family, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1903 January-1906 March (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1906 April (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1906 August-1909 September (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1910-1911 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1914-1915 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1916-1920 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1912 January-1912 June (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1912 July-1912 September (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1912 October-1912 December (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1913 January-1913 April (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1913 May-1913 December (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, before 1920 (Box 13, Folder 8-10)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to children, undated (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Anson Phelps Stokes to Helen Louisa Phelps Stokes; Hampton Institute (refusing position), undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to children, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1920-1927 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Anna V. S. Mitchell, 1897-1908 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Anna V. S. Mitchell, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Clarence Green Mitchell and Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1885-1893 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1886-1900 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1901-1920 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 13, Folder 21-25)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes to Isaac Newton Phelps Stokes, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes and others to Sarah Rood, 1881-1893 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Caroline Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1883-1890 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Caroline Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1887-1888 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Helen Louisa Phelps Stokes to Anson Phelps Stokes, 1907-1920 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Helen Louisa Phelps Stokes to Anson Phelps Stokes and Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1905-1920 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Helen Louisa Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1904-1920 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Helen Louisa Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, 1910-1920 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Olivia Eggleston Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1881-1897 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Olivia Eggleston Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, 1879-1897 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Olivia Eggleston Phelps Stokes to Sarah Lindley Mitchell, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Olivia Eggleston Phelps Stokes to Caroline Mitchell Phelps Stokes, Anson Phelps Stokes, and Olivia Stokes Hatch, 1897-1920 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Phelps Stokes family to Mitchell family, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - A. L. Wilson to Clarence Green Mitchell; Mary Lindley to Clarence Green Mitchell, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)